Jannaeé Sick

Front-End Developer and User Experience Designer with a keen eye for detail and a passion for clean user centric design. Demonstrates working knowledge of HTML/CSS, JavaScript and Git.

Raleigh, North Carolina (904) 994-5220 jannaee@gmail.com jannaee.github.io linkedin.com/in/jannaee

RELEVANT COURSEWORK

Udacity.com, Online Student

JAN 2018 - PRESENT

Grow with Google Mobile Web Specialist

Currently building a mobile web application featuring offline functionality, ARIA rich content, responsive images, CSS Grids and Flexbox.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tinsy Co, Raleigh NC

MAY 2014 - PRESENT

President and Owner of Tinsy Co.

Started a company that would specialize in leveraging 3D technology to create one of a kind and personalized pet memorial and celebration jewelry.

EverBank, Jacksonville FL

MAY 2012 - MAY 2014

Front-End Developer

Managed and developed dynamic rate banners, sortable tables and maintained other infographics reflecting the most up to date information.

Debugged JavaScript based features on product landing pages to enable seamless user experiences.

Zappos, Henderson NV

JUN 2012 - AUG 2012

Front-End Developer Intern

One of 13 interns chosen to learn core Front-End development practices by Senior Zappos Engineers and User Experience Researchers.

Built prototypes of a customer review functionality on 6pm.com using HTML/CSS/Javascript.

EverBank, Jacksonville FL

SEPT 2008 - MAY 2012

Digital UX Designer

Applied user centered research and 'mobile first' design best practices on over 6 websites as well as created interactive website elements using HTML/CSS/JavaScript.

Improved change control process by implementing templates for over 3 teams to use and reduced workload by 8 for 4 designers resulting in a streamlined workflow with 90% less discrepancies.

Built guides documenting the team's most common workflows in order to help new hires quickly become acquainted with common tasks and reducing the time to onboard by approximately 50%.

SKILLS

AWS Cloud9 IDE
Node.js, NPM, Grunt
ARIA Design Practices
Coremetrics
Adobe Creative Cloud
Customer Engagement
Training from Walt Disney
World

AWARDS

2018 Grow with Google Developer Challenge Scholarship Recipient Awarded 1 of 5,000 Developer Scholarships by Google.

2018 Grow with Google
Developer Challenge
Scholarship <u>"Student</u>
Stories Winner" Essay
chosen by peers as one of
the most inspirational
stories.

EDUCATION

Udacity.com

JAN 2018 - OCT 2018 (anticipated)

Mobile Web Specialist student seeking to earn a Nanodegree certification

University of North Florida

AUG 2000 - DEC 2004

Earned Bachelors of Fine Arts in Graphic Design with a 3.4 GPA

Honors Program Award Recipient

Graphical User Interface Designer

Created low fidelity wireframes for website redesigns, collaborated with external design agencies to ensure adherence to company's style guidelines.

Created and maintained Marketing and Communications trade show backdrops, pamphlets, banners, newsletters and invitations.